live I like to say welcome everybody to
another Wednesday
Q&A well we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God had written for
the whole world to keep brother
tanzel and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage thou shall
have no other gods before me thou shall
not make it to thee any Graven image or
any is of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
thou shall not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them oh I the Lord thy God am
a jealous God visiting the iniquities of
the fathers upon the children unto the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me and showing Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments thou shall not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him Guiltless that
take up his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
should thy labor and do all thy work but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of the
Lord thy God in it thou shall not do any
work thou Know Thy son nor thy daughter
thy man servant nor thy maid servant nor
thy cattle nor thy stranger that is
within thy gates for in six days the
Lord made Heaven and Earth the sea and
all that in them is and rest the seventh
day wherefore the Lord bless the Sabbath
day and holiday honor thy father and thy
mother that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee thou shall not kill thou shall not
commit adultery thou shall not steal
thou sh not bear false witness against
thy neighbor thou not cover thy
neighbor's house thou not cover thy
neighbor's wife no his man servant nor
his maid servant no his Ox no his ass
nor anything that is thy neighbors we
read Exodus
21-7 may the Lord have a blessing to the
reading of his words in Jesus name we
pray amen
amen so we like to say welcome brothers
and sisters to another Wednesday
question and answer and here on question
and answer you can ask us a question and
we'll answer it according to the King
James Bible and if we cannot find the
answer we will seek further counsel to
bring you an answer at a later time keep
in mind that all V questions will not be
answered all along scripture questions
will not be answered for time's sake but
we may be able to point you in the
direction of a DVD or a CD that you can
purchase by calling office so for time
sake please be as direct as possible
with your questions out of the King
James Bible so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of that
same Bible no other Bibles will be
acknowledged on this program also keep
in mind that this is a live stream and
you may begin to send in your questions
at this time even questions that pertain
to everlasting life we're just asking
you to keep your questions to a two
scripture minimum but let me introduce
you the family that's on the panel this
evening we got brother Jerome Grace and
peace Brother Dre good
evening uh brother Julius
he's present with us she'll be back
shortly brother
tanzel good evening sister
Deborah good
evening and we have brother Sean with
us good evening and the guest caller and
I'm brother
Cornell sister let us begin with our
first question of the evening uh yes
there are several questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A okay so the J related
person as in Jeremiah 31 Deborah can you
hold that for a second let's go let's go
to let's go directly to number two give
Julius a chance to uh come back on with
us let's go directly
second all right silent I wants to
know in Psalms 84
verse1 is that talking about second
Peter 3 verse
8 all right in that Psalms 84 and10 is
that talking about second Peter 3 and 8
brother Dre what you
got let's go read uh Psalms 84 and 10
and then we'll go to that second Peter
and take a look at both of them all
right so tanel go to Psalm 84 and read
verse
10 okay
for a day in thy courts is better than a
thousand I had rather be a doorkeeper in
the house of my God than to dwell in the
tents of
wickedness yeah day in the court in the
Lord's House is better than a thousand
in the tense of the Wicked This is what
he's saying here let's go to Second
Peter now the third chapter second Peter
3 and we're going to read verse 8 second
Peter 3 and verse
8 go ahead when you get it
brother but beloved be not ignorant of
this one thing that one day is with the
Lord as a thousand years and a thousand
years as one
day right so when we when we read both
of these scriptures they're not talking
about the same thing one is talking
about a thousand years being one day
with the Lord and the other one is
talking about being in the Lord's House
is one day is better than being there a
thousand years I mean being a a thousand
days in the house of the wicked you know
so let's just read one more place let's
go to Psalm
27 Psalm
27 and we're going to read verses four
and five Psalm 274 and5 you get it go
ahead
brother Psalms 274 and5 yes
sir what thing have I desired of the
Lord that will I seek after that I may
dwell in the house of the Lord all the
days of my life to behold the beauty of
the Lord and to inquire in his Temple
yeah go ahead for in the time of trouble
he shall hide me in his Pavilion in the
secret of his Tabernacle shall he hide
me he shall set me up upon a rock so it
ain't no better place to be than in the
house of the Lord and you know all the
days of his life to behold the beauty of
his way and his word so I hope that that
helps I hope that answers your question
I'm G give it back to Cornell
Cornell all right I want to add one
thing uh Psalms 90 and verse four I
think that kind of connects with that
second Peter yes
sir Psalm
99 and verse
four yeah all
right it reads thousand years in thy
sight are but are but as yesterday when
it is passed and as a watch in the
night yes
sir yep oh yeah second Peter brother
absolutely
yeah all right thank you for that add on
there brother and we hope that that U
shares some light there Deborah what you
say uh is um brother Julius back if not
I can go to the next question uh which
is I'm back which is Let's uh let's skip
up to
one skip back up to our original first
question all right number one says the
jar related at
uh
the the job related as in Jeremiah 31
verse 33 is this for present day or
during Jesus
Kingdom all right Jeremiah 31 tell us
brother is that uh
present yes sir tzel I apologize have
internet problems tanzel let's go to
Jeremiah 31 and the question is coming
from Jeremiah
31-33 and but what we going to do we
going to pick it up at verse 31 and read
on into
it okay Jeremiah 31 and 31 uhuh behold
the days come sayeth the Lord that I
will make a New Covenant with the house
of Israel and with the house of Judah
not according to the Covenant that I
made with their fathers in the day that
I took them by the hand to bring them
out of the land of Egypt
which my Covenant they break although I
was a husband unto them say the Lord
uhhuh but this shall be the Covenant
that I will make with the house of
Israel after those days sayth the Lord I
will put my law in their inward parts
and write it in their hearts and will be
their God and they shall be my people so
now the answer to that question is yes
this is for present day and and forward
from present day even on it Christ
kingdoms so therefore the old Covenant
was made with the fathers that came out
of Egypt under the hand of Moses which
was the animal
sacrifice and now the New Covenant I'mma
put the laws in your in P in other words
I'm going teach you and write them in in
your mind so now we know that that has
happened how do we know let's go to 1
Corinthians chapter
2 Jesus shed his blood on the C on on
the cross
that ended the old Covenant the bear was
ripped from top to bottom that ended the
old covenant made with the fathers on
the animal sacrifice and now we're under
the mees that priesthood of the Jesus
priesthood now we're under that Covenant
this New Covenant well he gonna teach us
how do I know let's go to the New
Testament and by the way you can find
the same thing that's written in Hebrews
the 8th chapter beginning at verse 6 but
we want this right here 1 Corinthians 2
let's work backwards 10 there verse 16
because this Covenant was fulfilled and
is being fulfilled now verse 16 go ahead
and read it for who have known the mind
of the Lord that he may instruct him
uhhuh we have the mind of Christ he said
Paul is saying but we have the mind of
Christ we under that old Covenant right
now verse 11 back up and read verse 11
and then verse 10 go
ahead for what man knoweth the things of
a man say the spirit of man which is in
him uhhuh H even so the things of God
knoweth no man but the spirit of God so
now how do we know we have the mind of
Christ and that we're under that New
Covenant go ahead but God have revealed
them unto us by his Spirit Oh by his
word go ahead for the spirit searcheth
all things yes yeah the Deep things of
God so we understand this New Covenant
we don't now we don't have to have the
Ten Commandments on Stone we got them in
our minds it already in our minds even
in your lap in the book and now you got
to know your smartphone so that we are
all without excuse so this the answer is
yes we are under this New Covenant now
and all into Christ Kingdom that's all I
got on that I hope that
helped all right thank you for that
there brother hope that answered their
question sister Deborah let's move on to
our next one yes moving on Ben uh elf
says is there reference to how the word
of God was studied by the Israelites as
a study guide in those times being that
the Bible we have today is a collection
of books written over about 1700 years
was it hell protected by
Levi all right brother Julius share some
light on um this book absolutely there's
always been reference to the word God uh
let's go to Isaiah the 34th chapter
let's read at verse 16 Isaiah
16 because it's always been referenc the
Lord had it written beginning from the
prophets all the way up to Revelation
from Genesis to
Revelation from Moses to John go ahead
and read Isaiah 34:16 what should we do
brother seek ye out of the book of the
Lord and read no one of these shall fail
uhhuh and None Shall want her M now
Isaiah is the Old Testament prophet and
the word uh Bible is a binding of books
but they had Scrolls back then let let
me show you what I'm talking about let's
go to Daniel the second chapter Daniel
chapter 2 and I got one place after this
uh Cornel all right Daniel chapter 2
remember the scripture say the prophets
are subject to the prophets
Daniel chapter 2 and read verse two
Daniel
2 verse two when you get it go ahead and
the King commanded to call the mic The
Magicians and the astrologers and the
sorcerers I'm sorry I'm sorry Daniel I'm
sorry Daniel 9
verse2 sorry about that Daniel 9
verse2 and the first year of his Reign I
now you understood by books the number
of the years where well the word of the
Lord came to Jeremiah the prophet that
he would accomplish 70 years in the
desolation of Jerusalem now Daniel said
he understand he understood by books
about the 70E prophecy he understood by
books because they always had uh uh
Scrolls right one more place one more
place because he's quoting Jeremiah the
25th chapter but one more place Luke the
4th chapter Daniel said that he
understand by books he read the the book
of Jeremiah or the scos of Jeremiah
concerning
the 70E prophecy Luke chapter
4 and this right here is absolutely
solid Luke 4 and pick it up my brother
at 16 we gonna read 16 and 17 when you
get it go ahead and he came to Nazareth
where he had been brought up and as his
custom was he went into the synagogue on
the Sabbath day and stood up for to read
this is Jesus go ahead and there was
deliver unto him the book of the prophet
Isaiah oh Jesus read the book of the
prophet Isaiah just like Daniel read the
book of The Prophet uh J Jeremiah go
ahead and when he had opened the book he
found the place where it is it was
written the spirit of the Lord is upon
me because he have anointed me to preach
the gospel to the poor he have sent me
to heal the brokenhearted to preach
Deliverance of the captives and
recovering of sight to the blind
to set at Liberty them that are
bruised and to preach the acceptable
year of the Lord that's good brother so
the answer is yes there is plenty of
reference from Genesis the Revelation
and Peter told you we have a more sure
word of Prophecy that you do well and
take heed holy men wrote as they were
moved by the holy spirit so the answer
is is always been yes right there always
been um uh uh references
pertaining to the word of God or the
what we call the Bible and your second
question read the second question again
Deborah all right
um was it only held or protected by
Levi it was Levi was the priest but the
nation was scattered but the Lord
created the whole nation of Israel to be
priests a whole nation of Kings and
Priests
so Levi was the lawgivers Judah was the
lawgiver Levi was the priest but the
whole nation was considered uh was
supposed to be a nation of Kings and
Priests one place Romans
nine Romans
n and we gonna read verses four and five
tenzel I hope this helps Romans 9 verses
four and five when you get it my brother
go ahead because Paul is telling you
about Paul the benjamite of the tribe of
the Israelite of the time of Benjamin is
telling you about who the oracles belong
to go
ahead who are Israelites the whom
pertaining the adoption and the glory
and the covenants and the giving of the
law and the service of God and the
promises and who else whose are the
fathers and of whom as concerning the
flesh Christ came who is over all God
bless forever amen and Jesus told you to
search the scripture for in them you
thinking have eternal life and all of
the prophets from Genesis the Revelation
testify of me the whole nation was a
nation of priest right Levi was
the set to uh give the word to the
people and then after they was scattered
everybody was supposed to have it like
we have it today that's all I got to
hope that
helps all right thank you for that
answer brother we're gonna move on to
our next question sister next question
he also ask is there any display of Edom
having a relationship with Rome in the
Bible Edom having a relationship with
Rome is that anywhere in the Bible
brother Dre yes sir yes sir let's go to
uh Matthew the 2 chapter Matthew the 2
chapter and we're gonna read
about this King that was appointed by
Rome over Jerusalem
mhm uh pick it up at verse one brother
tanel when you get it go
ahead now when Jesus was born in
Bethlehem of Judea in the days of Herod
the king behold there came wise men from
the East to
Jerusalem saying where is he that is
born King of the Jews for we have seen
his star in the east and I come to
worship him go ahead read
ver go
verse
three when Herod the king had heard
these things he was troubled and all
Jerusalem with him yeah Herod you should
look Herod up do some research on Herod
Herod was an
Edomite appointed by Rome to be king
over Jerusalem and I looked at a couple
of thing I looked at something here it
says here that the were
conquered forcibly and converted by
haonan Kings a couple of generations
before Herod was born he was ancestrally
an Edomite and religiously and by
identity a Jew but he wasn't a Jew he
converted his family did and he was
appointed King of the Jews by Rome
during that
time so I I I would uh call for you to
do some research on aod and you see that
Edom is right there that's all I
got all right brother thank you for that
answer I hope that answered that
question next
question yes Israelite Black by Blood
Brandon ask does the sabath begin when
it's completely dark also are we able to
use microwaves on the Sabbath
okay let's start with that first one
does the Sabbath begin when it's
completely dark the answer is
yes Sabbath does not begin when the sun
set because the sun rises in the East
sets in the west and once the sun is
down and you look to the West sometimes
you still got a whole lot of daylight
over there that has not begun the
Sabbath day it needs to be dark but
let's go back to uh the first book in
the Bible tanzel
and let's go to that Genesis 1 and let's
pick it up at verse
one Genesis 1 and pick it up at verse
one go ahead in the beginning God
created the Heaven and the Earth Yep and
the Earth was without form and void and
darkness was upon the face of the deep
and the spirit of God moved upon the
face of the waters and God said let
there be light and there was light so we
see everything was dark and the Lord
spoke light and there was light go ahead
and God saw the light that it was good
and God divided the light from the
darkness and God called The Light Dark
the light day and the Darkness he called
night and the evening and the morning
were the first day so we we see that God
called the light day and the Darkness he
called night and the evening and the
morning were the first day and when you
go and do some research on evening
evening is the beginning of
night
read and God said let there be a Firmin
in the midst of the waters and let it
divide the waters from the
waters and God made skip down skip down
brother that's good skip down to verse
16 because God is going to make two
great lights here sun and the moon go
ahead and God made two great lights the
greater light to Rule the Day and the
Lesser light to rule the night and made
the Stars also
uhhuh and God set them in the firmament
of the heaven to give light upon the
Earth and to rule over the day and over
the night and to divide the light from
the darkness and God saw that it was
good so God is dividing the light from
the darkness he didn't mention anything
about in between he said light or
darkness and so we start our Sabbath on
Friday once it's dark out not once the
sunset turn over to job 7 right quick
job the 7th
chapter because it can't still be light
out on Friday and you saying that the
Sabbath has begun you have to wait until
it's dark out job 7 and pick it up
brother at verse
four and let's see because night and
light don't dwell together let's see
what job said in verse four go
ahead when I lie down I say when shall I
arise and the night be gone and I am
full of tossing to and fro until the
dawning of the day oh so night is gone
once day starts to come in and day is
gone once night starts to kick in one
more Proverbs 7 and9 read that one verse
Proverbs 7 and
nine this is when the Sabbath day begins
as you were asking about you know when
does it begin when it's completely dark
go ahead tzel 7
and9 in the Twilight in the evening in
the black and dark night that's when the
Sabbath begins once it's dark out and
Twilight in the evening and like I say
evening is the beginning of night it's
not while it's still light out so yes it
has to be completely dark on Friday
night for the Sabbath to kick in now as
far as you asking about your microwave
on the Sabbath day the answer is
absolutely not you can cook a full meal
inside the microwave the Lord want wants
us to plan plan for his day so on Friday
before it gets dark out and the Sabbath
kick in have your meal already prepared
that microwave aside don't even use it
right prepare for the Lord's holy
Sabbath day as he calls it and therefore
hey you'll be in order with God that's
all I got and the full name is microwave
oven that's right microwave oven
that's correct brother thank you for
that hope that ansed your question as we
keep
moving uh yes uh Zan asks could you
please explain Genesis 3 vers 14 and 15
if the serpent is an actual person why
is he cursed above every beast of the
field also verse 15 the bruising of her
head and his heel means what all right
why don't we go to Genesis 3
tanzel and when you get there read that
verse 14 and the guest caller will take
it from
there Genesis 3
verse4 yeah and the Lord God said unto
the Ser because thou has done this thou
are cursed above all cattle and above
every beast of the field upon thy belly
shall thou go and dust shall thou eat
all the days of thy
life now let's uh the question was is is
this just if this is a person why was he
cursed above everything a beast of the
field this is not just a person let's go
show you who this serpent is let's go
into Revelation the 12th chapter and
read verse 9
read it when you get
there Revelation
12 and verse 9 when you get there
brother and the Great Dragon was cast
out that old serpent called the devil
and Satan
was so he wasn't a p a regular person
that was Satan devil that's what that
that serpent was in the Garden of Eden
that's just one of his many
names okay y just
a regular person he's the one that tried
to kill the whole creation well actually
did he have to come and save let's go
and read verse 15
now and I will put imity between thee
and the woman and between thy seed and
her seed and it shall bruise thy head
and thou shall bruise his
heel now it's going to be IM between the
woman her
seed and her seed now he say it your uh
uh brw uh uh her seed's heel not her
heel and her seed going to bruise bruise
his head so let's go and find out who
this woman is and who her seed is let's
go to revelation 12th chapter back to
Revelation 12th chapter and we going to
read 1 through3 and Skip down to
five read when they get
there and there appeared a great woman
in heaven a woman closed with the Son
and the moon under her feet and upon her
head a crown of 12
stars and she being with child C
TR on your own you can go to uh uh
Genesis the 37th chapter to let you know
that this woman is
Israel okay that's why the 12 the 12
stars represent the 12 uh tribes of
Israel and the sun represent Jacob and
the Moon represent his wife so this
woman she she travail side back there
would she travail in labor go
ahead and she being with child cry
travailing in birth and pain to be
delivered and there
now skip
down verse five and go
ahead and she brought forth a man child
who was to rule all nations with a rod
of iron and her child was caught up
under God into his
throne now this this man child is Jesus
he is the uh Jesus was an Israelite the
woman with the TW and the woman is
Israel so he came and he the rule All
Nation with the rod of ir but he died
before he went back to Heaven that's how
he end up getting his uh getting his
heel bruised you know you can bruise
somebody's heel and they can recover
from it but if you the head can't
recover from that now let me show you
what I'm talking about let's go into uh
uh uh let's go into Micah the 5th
chapter I read
[Music]
verse start at verse
one Micah 5 and
one now GA
thyself Micah 5 and
one now now gather thyself in truths oh
daughter of
truths he have laid seeds against us
they shall Smite the judge of th of
Israel with the rod upon the
cheek read
before but thou Bethlehem eph though
thou be little among the thousands of
Judah yet out of the shall he come forth
unto me that is to be ruler in Israel
whose going forth has been from of old
from
Everlasting but vers that that was in
the
two go ahead therefore would he give
them up until the time that she which
travel have brought forth then the
remnant of his brother shall return unto
the children of
Israel uhhuh and he shall stand and feed
in the strength of the Lord in the Maj
Majesty of the name of the Lord his God
and they shall abide for now shall he be
great unto the ends of the
Earth well let know this same
Manchild he is talking about Jesus he
going going Smite the judge of uh Israel
on the cheek other words he going to
spite him but he ain't but he going to
be crucified but he going to come back
and let me show you what going to happen
but God did he said he going to bruise
his hell let's go into uh Isaiah the
53rd chapter we going to read verse five
then we're going to skip down and read
verse 10 and this is talking about the
same Jesus read it when you get
there but he was wounded for our
transgression and he was bruised for our
iniquities the chastisement of our peace
was upon him and with his strength we
are
healed uhuh skip down to verse 10 yet it
pleased the Lord to bruise him he had
put him to grief where thou shall make
his soul an offering for
sin he shall see seeed he shall prolong
his
days now that bruising the heels I can
say the Lord is the one that bruis him
okay why is why they say Satan bruis him
because Satan caus e sin that mean that
Jesus had to come and die for the sins
of the people that's why I tell you in
Revelation uh uh uh Jesus uh uh slain
from the foundation of the world but
when you bruise somebody's heal they
recover
but when you bruise their head they will
not recover now like a seed now like a
seed the people that falling her seed
they going to bruise also
Satan by following Jesus let's go to
Romans the 16 and read verse
20 Romans
16 and 20
and the God of Peace shall bruise Satan
under your feet shortly the grace of our
Lord Jesus Christ be with you
amen so now God is going to bruise Satan
under Ser under the feet of his servant
he's going to bruise his head because
when he deal with Satan Ain no coming
back from that when he make his final
move on Satan let me show you that move
let's go into Revelation the 20th
chapter and read
verse
7-10 Revelation 20 verse
7-10 and with a thousand years I expired
Satan should be loosed out of his prison
and shall go out to deceive the Nations
which are in the four quarters of the
earth go and MOG to gather them together
to battle the number of whom is as the
sand of the
sea and they went up on the bre of the
earth and Compass the camp of the Saints
about and the Beloved City fire came
down from God out of heaven and devour
them and the devil that deceiveth them
was cast into the lake of fire and
brimstone where the Beast and the false
prophet are and shall be tormented day
and night forever and ever so that's
that's when the Lord's going to bruise
his head he gonna throw him in the Lake
of Fire and he will never come back
right so
so Satan bruised Jesus heal by making it
necessary for him to come and be
crucified but he rose from the dead and
he's the one that end up throwing Satan
in the Lake of Fire so that's how ITA
his he was bruised by having to die and
Satan head head was bruised is when the
Lord threw him in L of fire and ain't no
coming back that's all I have to say all
right hope that good light answers your
question
as we continue to move on with the time
check yes the time is 806 jiger Israel
ask what is Isaiah 60:
11-13 talking about is that the kingdom
of heaven and will the Gentiles be
building walls for the Israelites in the
Kingdom of
Heaven well Jerome share some light on
that Isaiah 61-13
no it's really talking about the uh
Kingdom of Jesus Christ uh the Son of
God uh and the location of that kingdom
is going to be on this Earth uh so but
let's go read those
verses in Isaiah 60 veres
11-13 you get it go
ahead therefore thy Gates shall be open
continually they shall not be shut day
nor night that men may bring unto
Thee the forces the force of the
Gentiles that their kings may be brought
for the Nations and kingdoms that will
not serve thee Shall Perish yeah those
Nations shall be utterly waste the glory
of Lebanon shall come unto thee the fur
tree the pine tree and the box together
to beautify the place of my sanctuary
and I will make the place at my feet
glorious yeah so specifically in that
Kingdom um in
Jerusalem this is what's going to be
going on when the Lord um return the
strangers going to be bringing all these
riches to beautify the
land
um um the forces of the Gentiles going
to be
brought to the people of God and to the
Lord to
Jerusalem uh so these are the things
that's going to be going on while the
Lord uh is in his kingdom which is on
this Earth okay
let's go to uh read that verse 14 for
me the sons also of them that afflict
thee shall come B bending unto thee and
all they that despise thee shall bow
themselves down at the souls of thy feet
and it shall call Thee the city of the
Lord the Zion of the Holy One of Israel
yeah and that city is specifically uh
Jerusalem which is called Zion skip to
verse 18
biding shall no more be heard in the
land wasting nor destruction within thy
borders but Thou shalt call thy walls
salvation and thy Gates
praise yeah and as far as the second
part of the question uh read verse verse
10 because the second part of the
question could you repeat that second
part
Deborah yes will the Gentiles be
building walls for the Israelites in the
Kingdom of
Heaven yeah read that verse 10 cuz
remember this is the son's Kingdom on
this Earth and this is going on going to
be going on in Jerusalem when the Lord
is back on this Earth dwelling in the
midst of the children of Israel in
Jerusalem but read that verse 10 and
answer that second part of the
question and the sons of strangers shall
build up thy walls and their King shall
Minister unto thee for in my wrath I
smoke thee but in my favor have I had
mercy on thee yeah and I I need to add I
need to add this for those that want to
think that when the stranger be in the
be among Israel that we going
to treat him with you know like slaves
like the African-Americans being treated
here now go to that Ezekiel and this
will be the last place go to that
Ezekiel 47 and read verse 22 and 23 cuz
yeah the strangers going to build your
walls but we going to treat them good
now and we going to hire them we're not
going to make them slaves and make them
work with Vigor okay uh Ezekiel 47: 22-
23 and it shall come to pass that ye
shall divide it by lot or an inheritance
unto you
and to the stranger that sour among you
which shall be got children among you
and they shall be unto you as born in
the country among the children of Israel
and they shall have inheritance with you
among the tribes of
Israel and and it shall come to pass
that in what tribe The Strangers sourth
there shall ye give him his inheritance
sayeth the Lord God yeah that's all I
got on
[Music]
that's right brother thank you some
strangers are mixed
multitude all right hope that answered
your question there sister Deborah let's
keep it moving yes and the time is
A2 Israel by Blood Brandon uh says when
it's time to flee to the Wilderness do
we go to the airport and revelation 12:4
14 is
given all right brother
Jerome the Lord will make a way share
some light
brother yeah um everybody on this planet
that got some understanding and and know
the flee to the Wilderness everybody's
situation and Circumstance ain't going
to be the same some might not have
access to the airport when they fleeing
trying to get to the Wilderness you know
so depending on what's available to them
wherever they are across this globe
that's what they got to use be it
airport airplane boat whatever you know
so but let's go read that verse that
they
gave what was it
Revelations Revelation 12 verse4 yeah
let's go read
that okay
okay and to the woman were given two
wings of a great Eagle that she might
fly into the wilderness
unto her place where she was nourished
for a time and times and half a time
from the face of the
servant yeah yeah so when she was
fleeing all across the globe those that
got understanding know def Fleet of the
Wilderness whatever they got access to
to get to their destination they going
to get helped by the Lord to get there
by any means possible some airports some
boats whatever okay now Matthews 24 go
to Matthews 24 and pick it up at
verse uh
16 go
ahead then let them which be in Judea
flee into the mountains go ahead and let
him which is on the housetop not come
down to take anything out of his
house neither let him which is in the
field return back to take his clothes
uhhuh and woe unto them that are with
child and to them that give suck in
those days yeah but pray pray ye that
your flights be not in the winter
neither on the Sabbath
day yeah cuz see these go it's going to
be urgent times in that time man where
people you know your your enemies the
enemies of of the people of God they
going to be trying to kill you so you
going doing a lot of hiding and running
so whatever you whatever you have
available to you to to Fleet that's what
you do okay that's all I got if anybody
want to add something they
can all right brother thank you for that
answer and uh the Lord want his people
to make it there so he will provide a
way amen all right hope that answered
your question next
question next question MC says I have
asked for repentance on something I did
over 30 years ago do I still need to ask
for repentance for that brother Julius
tell us about this merciful god yes he
is a merciful god and I think the
question that you really want to ask is
you have asked for
forgiveness repentance and forgiveness
is two different definitions you said
you have asked for repentance you have
asked for forgiveness on something you
did 30 years ago do you still need to
ask for
forgiveness for this well let's look at
what the Lord said let's go to Ezekiel
the 18th
chapter somewhere you
transgressed as we all do or have and
you want to be forgiven but you got to
stop repent means to stop sinning
against God have a change of
mind because the wages of sin is death
Ezekiel the 18th chapter and let's get
right to the point Tel verse
23 when you get it go
ahead have I any pleasure at all that
the wicked should die sayeth the Lord
say the Lord God and not that he should
return from his ways and live so what
you got to do at verse 21 21 go ahead
but if the wicked W will turn from all
his sins that he have committed and keep
all my statutes and do that which is
lawful and right he shall live he shall
not die
22 all his transgression that he have
committed they shall be that shall not
be mentioned unto him in his
righteousness that he have done he shall
live because the Lord like brother
Cornell said is a merciful god not
willing that anyone should perish let's
look at what Peter said let's go to acts
two acts
two and we GNA get right to the point on
this one
when You' when your conscience bothers
you so much and it bothers you because
if you ask for forgiveness and you go
and sin no more then and you repent be
baptized in the name of Jesus look what
the book said verse 38 Acts 2 and
38 then Peter said unto them repent and
be baptized every one of you in the name
of Jesus Christ for the remission of
sins and you shall receive the GI gift
of the Holy Ghost and when you receive
the gift of the Holy Ghost it will lead
and guide you into all truths so that
you don't purposely go and sin no more
right so therefore you don't want that
hanging over your head 30 years ago if
you repent if you found out you was you
had transgressed you repented you you
asked God for forgiveness in Jesus name
you know and uh you go and sin no more
well for for whatever reason maybe you
have not let that go uh something that
happened 30 years ago so you have to
repent be baptized in the name of Jesus
for for forgiveness of sins and move on
with your life and go and sin no more
anybody want to add to
that oh that was it brother thank you
for that hope they understood that and
let us keep moving sister Deborah yes
let's keep moving jalah said a Jehovah
Witness came to my house saying that I
needed to learn how to expose the devil
and his lives reading from their book I
gave Ecclesiastes 12 verses 13 and 14
they left my door need other scriptures
please let caller can you share some
light on this Jehovah Witness
encounter well let's go first and read
scriptures he talking
about we going to see what there's a
good answer
all right Ecclesiastes 12 ver 13 and
14 read it let us hear the conclusion of
the whole matter fear God and keep his
Commandments for this is the whole duty
of man for God shall bring every work
into judgment with every secret things
whether it be good or whether it be
evil that's why they left you door that
was a good answer but as far as reading
they book
find out by sat I'm going to show you
what book you going to be judged out of
go to Revelation 208th chapter read
verses
11-2 Revelation 20:
11-2 and I saw a great white throne in
him that sat on it from whose face the
earth and the heavens bled away and
there was found no place for them but I
saw the dead small and great stand
before God and the books were open and
another book was open which is The Book
of Life and the dead were judged out of
those things which were written in the
books according to their works so now
the books you gonna be judged out of it
is King James the books from Genesis to
Revelation I would suggest you read this
book this King James virgin from Genesis
the Revelation because this is the book
that you going to be judged out of by
the things that are written in this
book that's all so you gave a good
answer and if they come again you read
this to him that's all I have to say all
right thank you for that hope that
answers your question as we move on to
our next yes she also asks are you
allowed to use a blender on the
Sabbath
no let's go and read that um Isaiah 58
because remember the Sabbath day you're
supposed to be preparing the day before
whatever you need to blend you can blend
on Friday and put it in your
refrigerator or in your freezer
whichever one you prefer but the the
blender goes in the same category with
the microwave and electric teapot and
the coffee pot all that stuff you put
all that away so that you can serve the
Lord Isaiah 58 and let's read that verse
13 so we can be reminded that the Lord
calls this his holy day right so prepare
on the day before go ahead brother and
thou turn away thy foot from the Sabbath
from doing thy Pleasures on my holy day
and call the Sabbath of the light the
holy of the Lord honorable and shall
honor him not doing thy own ways nor
finding thy own Pleasures nor speaking
thy own
words then shall then shalt thou Delight
thyself in the Lord and I will cause
thee to ride upon the high places of the
earth and feed thee with the heritage of
Jacob thy father for the mouth of the
Lord have spoken it yeah so do you a
good job of planning do all your
planning before Friday before it's dark
everything that you want to do
pertaining to the Lord's Sabbath day so
that you can keep it as holy as possible
unto the Lord and that's all I
get and we go keep it moving sister de
yes simply bless ass how are we supposed
to keep Zephaniah 2 verses 1 two and
three if there's no Israel of God in
Oklahoma no Israel God in Oklahoma let's
go to that Zephaniah 2 pick it up at one
and the guest callers go take it from
there brother tanzel
Zephaniah 2 verse one yep gather
yourselves together yeah gather together
oh Nation not
desire go ahead keep
read before the decree bring forth
before the day pass after the Sha before
the fierce anger of the Lord come upon
you before the day of the Lord anger
come upon you
she seek ye the Lord all ye Meek of the
earth which hath WTH is Judgment seek
righteous but did you stop what did you
it was one through three did you get the
three yet I was I was right in the
middle of three go finish
it seek righteousness seek
meekness it may be ye shall be hid in
the day of the Lord's
anger okay don't thing I can tell you if
you don't have Israeli G close to you
then keep doing what you're doing
catching Us on YouTube on the
internet and observe the sabbath day
just like you was sitting here with us
and don't uh pollute this sabath
day and catch the
program and we pray the Lord that the
Israeli God have an opportunity to put a
church there that's the only answer I
can give you
all right thank you for that hope that
ansed your question as we keep
moving yes Evan Lee Bon senior says how
why am I having so much push back about
the dietary law they stand on Mark 7
vers 18 and
19 Jerome is always some Kickback
against the truth what you got yeah you
know they
deceived from the truth of the matter uh
let's go read the verse mark 718-
19 Mark 18 19 and he said unto them are
ye so without understanding also do you
not perceive that whatsoever thing from
without entent the man it cannot defile
him what's going
on because it entereth not into his
heart but into the Bel and go out into
the
drought see so in that 19th verse it
said because it enter not into his
heart and that's the real message the
Lord want you to get out of this okay
because what you eat with your mouth
whatever kind of food you eating with
your mouth be it the foods the Lord said
don't eat or the foods he said you can
eat it don't literally go into your
heart when you eat it do it it literally
go into your stomach then go out in the
drought okay but what he really talking
about defiling you is breaking his
Commandments going against what he say
do and that's what's defiling you okay
so go to the uh 21st verse read to the
23 go ahead
for from within out of the heart of men
perceived evil thoughts adulteries
fornication murderers theft covetousness
wickedness deceit lasciviousness an evil
eye blasphemy proud foolishness all
these evil things come from within and
defile the man yeah that's what he
really trying to tell you that's the
message you know and then the Lord tell
us in his Commandments he said
don't eat any swine he said that in his
Commandments and the Lord I think it's
in Hebrews the 13th chapter verse 8 he
said he the Lord he the same yesterday
today and
forever right okay he don't change okay
so if he don't want you to eat pork then
he don't want you to eat pork now he
ain't gonna want you to eat pork later
in the future okay so but when you do
that that's what's defiling you cuz you
breaking that
commandment okay uh read that Isaiah 66
verse Isaiah
66 and this is when the Lord
returned and he GNA show you how he feel
about it because he don't like I said he
don't change right Isaiah 66 read verse
15-1
17 for behold the Lord will come with
fire and with his CH is like a whirlwind
to render his anger with Fury and his
rebuke with flames of fire
for by fire and by his sword will the
Lord plead with All Flesh and the slain
of the Lord shall be many and they that
sanctify themselves and purify
themselves in the garden behind one tree
in the midst eating swine flesh and the
Abomination and the mouth shall be
consumed together sayeth the
Lord yeah so you know when you get a
chance read that Leviticus the 11th
chapter it it'll give what we call a
dietary law what you can and cannot eat
what's considered unclean to the Lord
that he don't want you to eat keep that
and and you'll be and you'll be good
don't keep it and you defiling yourself
that's right that's all I
got all right thank you for that brother
and it's also in that Deuteronomy 14 but
you stay strong and push back against
the truth hey that's a normal thing
sometime you stay strong
all right thank you for that brother as
we move on
sister yes Barbara steel says in the
Bible where they talk about the servants
that got their Master more talents
versus the versus the one that only got
one Talent was that symbolic for
Christians helping Souls come to Christ
she also says so what if you sit and
worry about you don't know of a soul you
brought to Christ when there could be a
seed you planted could you ever really
know if you get the
credit very interesting question there
Dre what you say I say let's go to First
Corinthians uh three First Corinthians 3
and and let's look at that the last
thing you said is important you know and
that that was a parable that that was
spoken of there but you got a talent and
you got something to say when God give
you to say it you won't be able to hold
back you gonna say it but let's go to uh
1 Corinthians 3 and pick it up at
uh verse uh verse seven let's just get
right down to
it verse six verse six
go ahead brother
Tel I have planted a Polish watered but
God gave the increase yeah so we plant
the
seeds Paul said I
plant Apollo's water the seed after he
planted it but it is God that gave the
increase y
brother go
ahead so then neither it neither is he
that planteth anything neither he that
water but God that giveth the
increase now he that planteth and he
that WTH are one and every man shall
receive his own reward according to his
own labor oh no doubt about that now in
terms of uh you getting this word and
and speaking it to somebody get this
word first first let's go to Psalms the
first chapter let's go to Psalms the
first chapter and we going to read
verses 1 through3 when you get this word
in you this is what's gonna
happen Psalms 1 1 through three go ahead
brother blessed is the man that walth
not in the counsel of the ungodly nor
standeth in the way of Sinners nor sth
in the seat of the scornful
but his Delight is in the law of the
Lord and in his law do he meditate day
and night so when you meditating on the
law day and night and you Delight in the
laws of God in the ways of God day and
night this is what's gonna happen to you
verse
three and he should be like a tree
planted by the rivers of water that
bringeth forth his fruit in his season
his Leaf also shall not wither and
whatsoever he doeth shall prosper I like
that part when he say he be like a tree
planted by the rivers of water that
bring forth fruit in this
season your work the the walk that you
got is a testimony about you so you just
keep keep learning in this word keep
walking in it keep planting seeds and
are watering them and God will will give
the increase don't don't worry about
that other stuff I hope it
helps all right thank you for that
brother and sister Deborah I believe we
getting ready to go into new
territory yes we are now into tonight's
Q&A for July the 10th
2024 Zion asks can we marry or date
Gentiles strangers or whatever they
their call I thought I heard the guest
caller say it's okay if we don't follow
after their
God all right what you say guest
caller no you didn't hear me say
that but I tell you what I
read let's go read
it let's go to Deuter the 7th
chapter read verse 1- 4
when the Lord thy God shall bring thee
into the land whether thou goest to
possess it and have cast out many
nations before Thee the Hittites and the
gites and the amorites and the
Canaanites and the pites and the hites
and the jebusites Seven Nations greater
and mighter than thou and when the Lord
thy God shall deliver them before thee
Thou shalt Smite them and and utterly
destroy them thou shall make no Covenant
with them nor show Mercy unto them
neither shall thou make marriages with
them thy daughters thou shall not give
unto his son nor his daughter shall thou
take unto thy son for they would turn
away thy son from following Mee that
they may serve other God so will the
angel of the Lord be kindled against you
and Destroy thee
suddenly and let me give you a good
example of a famous
that that did happen because he start
dealing he may had a lot of strange
wives so let's go into First Kings the
11th
chapter read 1 through six and we going
to skip down to verse
11 verse King the 11th chapter
1-6 then we skip down to verse 11 read
it when you get there but King Solomon
loved many strange women together with
the daughter of pharaoh women of the
mobites the ammonites the the
zidon zidonians and Hittites of the
Nations concerning which the Lord said
unto the children of Israel you shall
not go into them neither shall Thou come
in unto you for surely they will turn
away your hearts after their gods
Solomon clave unto these in love and he
had 700 wives princesses and 300
concubines and his wives turned away his
heart
for it came to pass and when Solomon was
old that his wife turned away his heart
after other gods and his heart was not
perfect with the Lord his God as was the
heart of David his father for Solomon
went after Estero the goddess of the
zidon zidonians and after meum the
abomination of the
ammonites and Solomon did evil in the
sight of the Lord and went not fully
after the Lord as did David his father
now Solomon didn't listen to
God he had all them strange wives and
when he got old they turned him away
from God he said he did evil in the
sight of the Lord and and and this is
the result skip down to verse 11 and
read wherefore the wherefore the Lord
said unto Solomon for as much as this is
done of thee and thou has not kept my
Covenant and my statutes which I have
commanded thee I will surely rent The
Kingdom from thee and will give it to
thy
servant now because of what colon did
fing after them strange gods for them
strange wives he had God split the
nation and is still split until this day
we went into captivity as a split nation
and we will be split until Jesus
returned now we're going to go one other
place and go to nemiah the 13th chapter
read verses 23- 27
neemi
13 23-
27 and the those days also saw I Jews
that had married wives of ashah and Amma
and of Moab and their children spake
half in the speech of ashdod and could
not speak in the Jews language but
according to the language of people and
I contended with them and cursed them
and smoked certain of them and plucked
off their hair and made them swear by
God saying ye shall not give your
daughters unto their sons nor take their
daughters unto your sons or for
yourselves did not Solomon king of
Israel sin by these things yet among
many nations was there no King like him
and was belov of his God and God made
him King over all Israel never
nevertheless even him did outlandish
women caused to sin shall we then
hearken unto you to do all these this
great evil to transgress against our God
and marrying strange
wives now that is what I
read now you make out of it what you
want to that's all I have to
say all right we're going to keep it
moving sister Deborah to our next one
next one Rand 64 asks what is going to
happen to the millions of kids who have
died since the beginning of time until
now will they be raised as adults in
their spiritual bodies and already be a
full adult yes
carer that answer you going to have to
wait till the Lord come but there's no
in the book that says one thing or
another concerning the question you
asked all right hope that answered you
question right there as we continue to
move
on yes mve T ask you to explain the
meaning of Matthew
24 vers 40 and
41 Matthew 2440 and 41 let's go there
brother tanzel
this is where people like to use the
word rapture at which is not even in the
Bible and does not apply to the Bible
period but Matthew
24 and when you get there brother let's
pick it up at that verse
37 and read down go right
ahead but as the days of no where so
shall also the coming of the son of man
be yeah for as in the days that were
before the flood they were eating and
drinking marrying and giving in marriage
until the day that no enter into the
ark Y and knew not until the flood came
and took them all away so shall also the
coming of the son of man be it was
having a good old time and party until
the water started
tanzel go ahead then shall two be in the
field the one shall be taken and the
other left so this is two that's in the
other left go ahead two women shall be
grinding at the meal the one shall be
taken and the other left all right go
ahead that's it read that next verse 42
and we go go to first Thessalonians go
ahead watch therefore for ye know not
what our your lord do come so this is
what we say is the first resurrection
for those that make the cut it's going
to be two standing there and one goingon
to make it and the other one will to be
left behind and let's see where we're
going to meet the Lord at because the
Big Show goes on on Earth 1
Thessalonians the 4th chapter
right and this also pertains to those
that have died thousands of years ago
but made to cut with the lord they're G
to also be a part of this uh meeting the
Lord in the clouds 1 Thessalonians
4 and uh let's pick it up um pick it up
at 14 go ahead brother for if we believe
that Jesus died and rose again even so
them also which sleep in Jesus will God
bring with them so the ones that have
died hey God gonna wake them up too and
they gonna leave this earth and meet the
Lord in the clouds go ahead but this we
say unto you by the word of the Lord
that we which are alive have remain un
to the coming of the Lord shall not
prevent them which are asleep uhhuh for
the Lord himself shall descend from
heaven with the Shout with the voice of
the Archangel and with the Trump of God
and the dead in Christ shall rise first
so when Lord star s the s coming down
then the dead in Christ is going to rise
first and when you saw the two women
grinding and one was left and two in the
field and one was left this is what
happened to them verse
17 then we which are alive and remain
shall be caught up together with them in
the clouds to meet the Lord in the air
and so shall we ever be with the Lord so
that is considered the first
resurrection where you GNA meet the Lord
in the clouds one woman got left behind
who didn't make the cut and the two that
did make the cut hey they're going to
meet the Lord in the clouds but we
coming right back down to the earth
right so that's some explanation for you
on that uh Matthew the 2440 and
41 and that's all I got and we're gonna
keep moving sister Deborah because time
is a tick in the next
question yes LS says my friend has a hus
my friend has her husband ashes in her
home how long am I clean for if I enter
her home if I see her outside away from
her home and greet her with a hug am I
unclean yes you are so if you go over to
your friend's house where she has her
husband ashes there and you walk into
her house if you don't touch the earn
but you just go to her house and you
leave you are unclean until the
evening definitely unclean because her
house is continually unclean 247 that
doesn't stop as long as she got that
earn in her home now if you see her out
somewhere and she just left her house
and she give you a big old hug you still
unclean until the
evening because the earn which is also
known as a keeper of the ashes which is
a body and Ash form hey it is
continually unclean where that house is
at God say for dust Thou Art and unto
dust Thou shalt return so all earns have
a place back to the dust and we hope
that your friend continues to listen to
you and make that happen so that she can
clean her own house and won't be putting
you at jeopardy with uncleanness until
the evening but that's all I got on that
brother
Cornel should she uh wash her flesh or
her clothes with for that evening come
yeah indeed brother thank you good catch
there so yes so when you go home you got
to you got to wash your flesh like
brother Jerome say and then at the
evening time you'll be clean even your
clothes and then you'll be clean thank
you
brother welcome all right we're gonna
move to our next
question yes D wlc
NTW ask can you please explain
Exodus 34 verse 7 also Exodus 20 verse5
what is the meaning behind the third and
fourth
generation brother Dre what you say
share some light yes sir let's go to uh
Exodus 34 and we're gonna read verses
six and seven and then we'll go to
uh uh Exodus 20 and5 go ahead brother
tanzel when you get it go
ahead and the Lord passed by before him
and proclaim the Lord Lord God merciful
and gracious
longsuffering and abundance and goodness
and
Truth keeping mercing for
thousands forgiving iniquity and
transgressors and sin and that will by
no means clear the
guilty visiting the iniquities of the
fathers upon the children
and upon the children's children unto
the third and fourth
generation now let's go over to Exodus
20 and we gonna read verse five Exodus
20 and verse 5 Exodus 20 and
verse read it when you get it
brother thou shall not bow down thyself
to them nor serve them why the Lord thy
God am a jealous God visiting the
iniquities of the fathers upon the
children
into the third and fourth generation of
them that hate me you know this third
and fourth generation
piece look if something happened to a
father the children are affected and if
the children are affected the children's
children are affected right God told us
something else that I want us to look at
in Ezekiel 18 let's go to Ezekiel
18 Ezekiel 18 and we're going to pick
pick it up at verse
one Ezekiel 18 and pick it up at one and
read to
three e
18 verse one yeah read it when you get
it
BR the word of the Lord came unto me
again saying what mean ye that you used
this proverb concerning the land of
Israel saying the fathers have eaten
sour grapes and the children's teeth are
set on
Edge as I live say the Lord God you
should not have occasion anymore to use
this proverb in Israel so in other words
the fathers then did something wrong and
now the children's teeth are set on edge
for what the fathers did read verse four
and we gonna
skip go
ahead behold All Souls are mine as the
soul of the father so also the soul of
the son is mine the soul that sinth it
shall die skip down to verse
18 as for his father because he cruy
oppressed spoiled his brother by
violence and he that which is not good
among his people Lo even he shall die in
his iniquity go ahead but yet say ye why
do not the son be iniquity of the
fathers well the son have done that
which is lawful and right and have kept
all my statute and have done them he
shall surely
live so in other words the son ain't
gonna pay for what the father did right
the son is gonna pay for what he does if
he does that which is lawful and
right he shall surely live the father
did what he did he G to pay for it go
ahead brother the soul that sinth it
shall die the son shall not bear the
iniquity of the fathers neither shall
the father bear the iniquity of the son
the righteousness of the
righteous shall be upon him and the
wickedness of the wicked shall be upon
him but if the wicked will turn from all
his sins that he have committed and keep
all my statutes and do that which is
lawful and right he shall surely live he
shall not die last verse go ahead all
his transgression that he have committed
they shall not be mentioned unto him in
his righteousness that he have done he
shall live so the Lord just want us to
turn you know each and every last one of
us I hope that answers your
question yes sir indeed all have sin
brother Dr so why not turn and serve God
yes sir all right hope that answered
your question next one sister
de next one Israelite woman ask can you
explain the Sabbath of the seventh year
and the Jubilee in the 15 year yes Carin
can you share some
light sure
can there ain't no Jubilee in the 15th
year now the seven Sabbath represent the
seven days
which is 7,000 years that God gave man
let's go into Leviticus the 23rd chapter
first and read verse
three and excuse me it should have been
the Jubilee in the 50th
year okay then that's
better 50th year
okay still read 23 and
three six days shall work be done but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of rest
and holy convocation ye shall do no work
therein it is the Sabbath of the Lord in
all your
dwelling now so the lord gave man seven
days and that's all man got which really
is 7,000 years so when you go to the uh
uh uh seven Sabbath it's saying the same
thing but it's just adding one thing to
it let's go first let's go going to uh
skip down to the uh uh and read the 10
and 12 verses of uh
uh Leviticus then we going to skip verse
10 and 12 2310 and
12 speakto the children of Israel and
say unto them when ye be come unto the
land which I give unto you and shall
reap the Harvest thereof and ye shall
bring a sheath of the first fruit of
your Harvest unto the the
priest and he shall wave the Sheep
before the Lord to be accepted for you
on the tomorrow after the Sabbath the
preach shall wave
it now it could only be waved tomorrow
after the Sabbath because when you come
into the Harvest the Lord using fruit
that come out of the ground as people
that are changed rais from the dead so
they are way before the Lord on tomorrow
after the Sabbath day which is eight
days get
down verse uh uh 14 and continue 14 and
read verses 14 and 16 read it and you
shall eat neither bread nor parch corn
nor green ears until the selfs same day
that ye have brought an offering unto
your God it should be a statute forever
throughout your generation and all your
dwelling verse 16
now but ver verse is it that was in the
okay read the next
one even un tomorrow after the seventh
Sabbath shall ye number 50 days and ye
shall offer a new meat offering unto the
Lord so now you make the offering and
then you uh uh uh do it on for seven
days until tomorrow after tomorrow after
the seventh day you make a new meat
offering all this is saying is that uh
uh did you finish that 16th verse
yes all this saying is the man got seven
days and on and after that seventh day
uh uh man don't exist no more everybody
become
Immortals and uh uh let's go and and
Paul can uh explain this to you also we
going to we're going to look at
this we going to pick it up at First
Corinthians the 15th
chapter oh this is from man's uh uh fall
in the Garden of
Eden until the father's Kingdom we're
going to read 1 Corinthians 15 verses
20-
28 go ahead and read it but now is
Christ risen from the dead and become
the first fruits of them that
slept for Since By Man Came Death by man
came also the resurrection of the Dead
do now remember now remember the first
the first fruit of your crops come out
of the ground these are the first fruit
of the Dead that died and he come out of
the ground so he's the first
fruit go ahead and read but as an Adam
all die even so in Christ shall all be
made
alive but every man in his own order
Christ the first fruits afterward they
that are Christ at his
coming then cometh theend now after
Christ is the first fruit ain't nobody
rose from the dead and live and continue
to live but him but then when Jesus come
you going to have a first resurrection
then you going to have a last
Resurrection now this is the rest of the
fruits going to come once that and then
he and the first resurrection he's going
to rule his Earth for a thousand years
at the end of the Thousand Years then he
going to have the last Resurrection
that's when you going to have a white
Throne judgment now once you had a white
Throne judgment now that's the end of
the seventh day because Jesus going rule
this Earth and complete it and complete
his rulership on the in the 7,000 years
at the end of the 7,000 years then he
going to then he going to present the uh
uh uh fruits of the Harvest to the
father now this one notice it said then
cometh the end start
there then cometh the end when he shall
have delivered up the kingdom to God
even the father when he shall have when
he shall have put down all rule in all
authority and
power for he must Reign he have put all
enemies under his
feet The Last Enemy that shall be
destroyed is
death now that's all happening on the
seventh day Last Enemy that's going to
be destroy is death go
ahead he put all other words there ain't
going to be no more dying go ahead for
he have put all things under his feet
but when he sayith all things I put unto
him it is manifested that he is expected
which did put all things unto
him when all things shall be subdued
unto him then shall the son also himself
be subject unto him that put all things
unto him that God may be all and
all now once Jesus finish his th Reign
on this Earth and he have had the first
and the last Resurrection he's going to
turn it all over to the father but that
is done
on of
Jubilee the Year of
Jubilee okay now and after that there
ain't going to be no more Mortals get
down to verse
15 I'm sorry let's go into uh uh First
Corinthian Revelation the 21st chapter
read 1- 4 Revelation 21
1-4 and I saw a new Heaven and a new
Earth but the first Heaven and the first
Earth were passed away and there was no
more
sea and I John saw the holy city New
Jerusalem coming down from God out of
Heaven pre prepared as a bride adorned
for her
husband I heard a great voice out of
Heaven saying behold the Tabernacles of
God is with men and he will dwell with
them and they shall be his people and
God himself shall be with them and be
their
God and God shall wipe away all tears
from their eyes and there shall be no
more death neither sorrow nor cry
neither shall there be any more pain for
the former things are passed
away now that is the end of it that is
the that when uh uh so the Year of
Jubilee is the eighth day that represent
the first day of the father's
Kingdom have to say all right thank you
for that answer there we got uh just a
couple of more questions that might
require just um might just be a couple
of short answers to it so let's see if
we can speed round um sister Deborah
what's the next
all right uh sander hering says one
brother says that the gospel consisting
of St Matthew Mark Luke and John is is
this correct and can you explain St John
verse2 Shall Believe on me through their
word brother Julius
Julius you on mute
the gospel uh consists uh the word
gospel means good news or Good
Tidings if you read each one of those
books that the brother named uh Matthew
Mark Luke and John it would tell you the
Gospel According to the Gospel According
to the Gospel According to and The
Gospel According to the gospel is the
good news what is the good news it
teaches the um test testimony of Jesus
Christ's Mission his teachings his life
and his Plan of Salvation for man which
are written in those
books uh which are written in those
books authored by those disciples but
the gospel is nothing new it's always
been here let's go to show you that it's
always been here let's go to Hebrews the
4th
chapter and then we'll read uh we'll
come back to that St John
17 Hebrews chapter
4 kenzel and
verse Hebrews 4 and we going to pick
this up at verse pick it up at verse one
Hebrews 4 and one will you get it go
ahead
brother let us therefore
fear lest a promise being left us of
entry into his rest any of you should
seem to come short of it and that rest
represents the kingdom of Christ go
ahead For unto us was the Gospel
preached as well as unto them oh so the
gospel didn't started Matthew Mark Luke
and
John it started in the wilderness For
unto us was the Gospel preached go ahead
as well as unto them uhuh but the word
preached did not profit them nor being
mixed with faith in them that heard it
because the fathers under the hand of
Moses and them and the father and the
Elders of Israel they didn't believe it
so then Jesus came in the flesh to
testify of himself which is what his
plan his mission and let's look at what
he testified of yourself last place
Isaiah 61 vers 1 2 and
3 that's why John the 5th chapter tell
you to search the
scriptures and in them are they that
testify of
me Isaiah 63 Isaiah 61 61 Isaiah 61
begin reading at verse 1 two and three
this is all about Jesus before he came
in the flesh and what his mission would
be go ahead Tel the spirit of the Lord
God is upon me because the Lord have
anointed me to preach a good Tiding unto
the meek he have sent me to bind up the
Brokenhearted to Proclaim liely to the
captive and the opening of the prison to
them that are bound
to proclaim the acceptable year of the
Lord and the day of Vengeance of our God
to comfort all that
more to appoint unto them that mourn in
Zion to give unto them Beauty for Ashes
the O of joy for mourning the Garment of
Praise for the spirit of
heaviness that they might be called
Trees of Righteousness the planting of
the Lord that he might be glorified and
Jesus fulfilled all of that and even
came and testified in Luke the 4th
chapter fulfill all of that in 3 and A2
years and gave and the answer that last
part of that question about St John 1720
let's go back there and read that
quickly St John 17 and 20 when you get
that tzel we're gonna read that John St
John 17 and verse
20 go ahead go ahead and read it neither
pray I for these alone but for them also
which Shall Believe on me through their
word and what is their word the gospel
of the kingdom of God and how do we do
that by believing what Jesus gave to His
prophets and to his uh disciples and
apostles so it's not their word it's
their testimony which is their word
which is what the gospel is the gospel
of the kingdom of God the coming of the
government of God upon this Earth and
that's all I got on that I hope that
helped yes sir all right thank you for
that sister Deborah quickly our next all
right read your Bible and pray every day
uh
ask I am divorcing my husband because he
committed adultery it he is not in the
truth if I wanted to am I able to get
remarried in the future after everything
is
finalized yes Cola
I'm going read three
scriptures let's go to Deuteronomy 24
read verse one and two Deuteronomy 24 1
and
two when a man have taken a wife and
marry her and it come to pass that she
find no favor in his eyes because he
have found some unclean as in her then
let him write her a bill of
divorcement and give it in her hand and
send her out of his
house and when she has departed out of
his house she may go and be another
man's
wife now let's go to Matthew the 19th
Chapter read verses
2-9
quickly Matthew 19
verse
two through
n
n and great multitudes followed him and
he healed them there the Pharisees also
came unto him tempting him and saying
unto him is it lawful for a man and put
away his wife for every cause and he
answered and said unto them have ye not
read that he which made them at the
beginning made them male and female now
and said for this cause shall a man
leave father and mother and shall cleave
to his wife and they twain shall be one
flesh wherefore they are no more Twain
but one flesh what therefore God have
joined together let no man put
aund and they said unto him but why did
Moses then command to give a right of
divorcement and to put her away and he
said unto them Moses because of the
hardens of your heart suffer you to put
away your wives but from the beginning
it was not so
I say unto you who whosoever shall put
away his wife accepted be for
fornication and shall marry another
committed for adultery who so marry her
which is put away do commit
adultery now let's go quickly the First
Corinthians the 7th chapter read verses
10- 15
[Music]
thing and unto the Mary I command yet
not I but the Lord let it not let not
the wife depart from her
husband but and if she depart let her
remain unmarried or be reconciled to her
husband and let not the husband put away
his wife but to the rest speak I not the
Lord if any brother have a wife that
believe not and she be pleased to dwell
with him let him not put her away and
the woman which have a husband that
believe not and if he be pleased to
dwell with her let her not leave him for
the unbelieving husband is Sanctified by
the wife and the unbelieving wife is
Sanctified by the husband else were your
children unclean but now are they holy
but if the unbelieving depart let them
depart a brother or sister is not under
bondage in such cases but God have
called us to peace
that's all I have to
say have a good evening all right have a
good evening thank
you yes and uh we are finished brother
uh Cornell that other question have
already been answered through
iog all right and we want to thank
everybody who tuned in with us this
evening we took joy in answering your
questions because we believe in quality
more than quantity
and if you submitted a question and we
didn't get to it please don't resubmit
it sister Deborah take it put it in
rotation and we'll get to it next week
so until we all come together again
please be safe out there be blessed and
may the Lord have mercy on us all close
us out brother T Our Father which are in
heaven Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom
come thy will be done in earth as it is
in heaven give us this day our daily
bread and forgive us of our debts as we
forgive our Deb to us and lead us not
into temptation but Deliver Us from Evil
for thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever in Jesus name we
pray